runbus.in 2015-03-21

# Privacy Policy of runBus.in

  * We are going to give complete importance to your trust which you place on us and our website. This is the reason we approach you with the secured transaction and also with some of the high standards as well. You can also read our policy to get to know the complete policy in terms of gathering your information. 

  * ### Important Note:

Our privacy policy can be change at point of the time without providing any further notices and you can be aware of any type of changes in the privacy policy by reviewing our policies.

If you are visiting our runbus.in website then you must agree with the conditions and also terms of our privacy policy otherwise you are not allowed to take the access of our website.

By using this website all your personal information is used as per the current accordance with privacy policy and also this policy get in corporate in terms of use. 

  * ### 1\. Anthology of your identification personal and another information 

We are going to store all your information related to the browsing so that we get some simple and ease to provide you the smooth, safe and also efficient user experience and thus allows us to provide some of the best services that you used more frequently to give you the better experience. 

You can come to see any type of details regarded to the bus or any another information without taking our permission and if you put your personal information then we can easily rectify you and if you don't want to give your personal information then it is also possible but for this you don't have to subscribe for any personal information but we are going to track some of the basic information based upon the website behavior and we are going to use this information on the basis of the interests and demographics for better serve to the users and we can calculate all this things with the help of the URL , computer browser information and your IP address. 

We do collect and check the cookies of our pages and we also have some of the specialized tool which are used to collect all the data from the cookies and use them to make our promotion effective and also provide some of the special feature which are provided with the help of the cookies. 

If you done any type of transaction through our website then we are going to collect few extra information as well which includes the number and expiration detail of the debit/ credit card, billing address and another necessary information as well and if you choose to put reviews or you go with the free account then we are going to use all this information to give you the special offers and to resolve dispute as well. 

  * ### 2\. Sharing Personal Information 

We are surely going to share all the personal contact information to all the companies to whom we have the complete faith and who will preserve and disclosure of information is reasonably necessary to 

For law or legal process. 

For detection of fraud, technical and security issues. 

To save in front of harm to rights. 

We are surely going to share all the personal contact information to all the companies to whom we have the complete faith and who will preserve and disclosure of information is reasonably necessary to 

  * ### 3\. For Security

All our data is get stored on a dedicated and secured server so that there would not be any type of chances for the information leak or even the data lost and thus we have some of the specialized anti- virus which are installed on our pc and thus our strict security will going to restrict any unwanted transfer of data. 

  * ### 4\. Your Consent 

All your information whether it is personal or professional will be used as per this privacy policy but not in the limited way.

We can decide to change all or a smaller part of the policy and post them here so you can come here and check whether the changes and circumstances in the policy which are disclose here.
